http://www.whatprice.co.uk/data/privacy.html

Whatprice.co.uk Privacy Policy
"The price sharing community"
Privacy Policy for www.whatprice.co.uk
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at webmaster@whatprice.co.uk. At www.whatprice.co.uk, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.whatprice.co.uk and how it is used. Log FilesLike many other Web sites, www.whatprice.co.uk makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. DoubleClick DART Cookie .:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.whatprice.co.uk..:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.whatprice.co.uk and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Some of our other advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.whatprice.co.uk send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.whatprice.co.uk has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.whatprice.co.uk's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
If you found this page useful please click the +1 button below to tell Google that its a great page!
Please share this page with others, and leave a comment, we value all feedback!
Was this page useful? Do you have something to add? Do you disagree?
If your comments meet our
guidelines then we will publish them (you do not need to register!)
Ttradesman -
click here to join our network to receive leads from customers in your area
Find a Tradesman!
